<resources>
    <string name="app_name">V2</string>
    <string name="prompt_password" />
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">\n</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in" />
    <string name="prompt_email" />
    <string name="invalid_password" />
    <string name="invalid_username" />
    <string name="login_failed" />
    <string name="welcome" />
    <string name="title_dashboard" />
    <string name="description">\n</string>
    <string name="medication" />
    <string name="emergency_contact" />
    <string name="date_of_admittance" />
    <string name="schedule_notification" />
    <string name="message" />
    <string name="title" />

    <string name="lady1">A list view is an adapter view that does not know the details, such as type and contents, of the views it contains.
        Instead list view requests views on demand from a ListAdapter as needed, such as to display new views as the
        user scrolls up or down. In order to display items in the list, call setAdapter(android.widget.ListAdapter)
        to associate an adapter with the list. For a simple example, see the discussion of filling an adapter view
        with text in the Layouts guide.</string>
    <string name="lady2">Checkboxes allow the user to select one or more options from a set.
        Typically, you should present each checkbox option in a vertical list. To create each checkbox option,
        create a CheckBox in your layout. Because a set of checkbox options allows the user to select multiple items,
        each checkbox is managed separately and you must register a click listener for each one.</string>
    <string name="lady3">ImageView class is used to display any kind of image resource in the android application
        either it can be android.graphics.Bitmap or android.graphics.drawable.Drawable
        (it is a general abstraction for anything that can be drawn in Android).
        ImageView class or android.widget.ImageView inherits the android.view.View class which is the subclass
        of Kotlin. AnyClass.Application of ImageView is also in applying tints to an image in order to reuse a
        drawable resource and create overlays on background images. Moreover, ImageView is also used to control
        the size and movement of an image.</string>
    <string name="lady4">A toggle button allows the user to change a setting between two states.
        You can add a basic toggle button to your layout with the ToggleButton object.
        Android 4.0 (API level 14) introduces another kind of toggle button called a switch that provides
        a slider control, which you can add with a Switch object.</string>
    <string name="add" />

</resources>